(Leonard:)Oh.
- God!
- Okay, look. No, Penny...
I think what you're feeling is valid
and maybe later today...
...when you're feeling less,
for lack of a better word, violated...
...maybe we can talk about this.
- Stay away from me.
- Sure. That's another way to go.
Penny, Penny, hold on.
(Sheldon:)Just to clarify...
(Sheldon:)...because there will be a discussion
when you leave.
(Sheldon:)Is your objection solely to our presence
in the apartment while you were sleeping...
(Sheldon:)...or do you also object to the imposition
of a new organizational paradigm?
[DOOR SLAMS]
(Sheldon:)Well, that was a little non-responsive.
(Leonard:)You are going to march yourself
over there right now and apologize.
[SHELDON LAUGHS]
(Leonard:)What's funny?
(Sheldon:)That wasn't sarcasm?
- No!
- Whoo.
(Sheldon:)Boy, you are all over the place
this morning.